e-miles.com 2015-03-22

# e-Miles: Earn miles for free and redeem towards your favorite reward program

This privacy policy applies to www.e-miles.com owned and operated by e-Miles, Inc. This privacy policy describes how e-Miles, Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site: www.e-miles.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

e-Miles, Inc. ("e-Miles") is firmly committed to protecting your privacy. Because protecting your privacy is important to us, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our privacy practices to [info@e-Miles.com](mailto:info@e-miles.com?subject=e-Miles%20Privacy%20Promise). If you choose to write us an e-mail, please reference the Privacy Policy in your subject line. e-Miles® will attempt to respond in a timely manner to all reasonable concerns and inquiries. 

e-Miles, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements ](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/)including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personally identifiable  
information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, www.e-miles.com.

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [info@e-Miles.com](mailto:info@e-miles.com?subject=e-Miles%20Privacy%20Promise). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [ TRUSTe here. ](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

e-Miles, Inc. complies with the U.S. — E.U. Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union member countries. e-Miles, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view e-Miles, Inc.’s certification, please visit [ http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/ ](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/)

_You Will Not be Spammed by e-Miles_  
The e-Miles Service (e-Miles Service) is an opt-in e-mail program. You will only receive e-mails from e-Miles based on information you supply to us. 

The Information We Collect and How We Use It 

Communications from the Site 

Non-Electronic Communications with You 

How to Edit or Correct Your Personally Identifiable Information 

We are Committed to Data Security 

We are Committed to Children's Privacy 

Our Opt-Out Policy 

Social Media Widgets 

Changes in the Privacy Policy 

Protection of e-Miles and Others 

How to Contact Us 

Privacy Policy Revised as of 03/26/2014
